

Md. Oahiduzzaman Mondol Zihad

Web Developer

https://github.com/OahidZihad khttps://oahidzihad.netlify.app/

Front-End Developer with a proven experience and ability to collaborate effectively with team members to ensure workloads. My ambition is to learn everything from scratch in order to create professional and mobile-first application with reusable functional code.

EDUCATION

North South University,

BSc in Computer Science & Engineering 2017 - 2021

Member: IEEE Passing Year: 2021 CGPA: 3.31 out of 4.00

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Skylark Soft Ltd, Frontend Developer Sep 2022 - present | Dhaka, Bangladesh

- Design and bug fixing of garments related ERP systems.
- Maintain and redesign different ERP, POS, HRM, CRM software based on customer's requirements.
- Maintain the best user experience by finding different pain points from the user interface.

Care-Box Limited, Frontend Developer Nov 2021 - Sep 2022 | Dhaka, Bangladesh

- Designs and creates software solutions to solve pain points and check feasibility of software prototypes.
- Manage clients technical requirements & sometimes collaborate with mobile app developers.

(P) SKILLS

Programming Languages:

C, C++, JavaScript

React Functionalities:

Context API, Redux, Hooks, React Router, React Animation

Frontend Web

Technologies:

React.is, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Material UI

Backend Web

Technologies:

Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Rest API

□ PUBLICATIONS

SmartOil: Blockchain & Smart Contract-based Oil **Supply Chain Management.,** Wiley, IET Blockchain *⊘*

- Journal Reference: IET Blockchain 2021
- DOI: 10.1049/blc2.12005

Revolutionizing the Industrial Internet of Things Using Blockchain: An Unified Approach,

Springer &

- Part of the Intelligent Systems Reference Library book series (ISRL, volume 215)
- DOI: 10.1007/978-3-030-90119-6_5

PROJECTS

https://care-box.com, Ecommerce Site ≥

https://e-doctor.io/, Digital Medical Service &

https://carebox-pathology.web.app,

Digital Pathology System &